Guide to the Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America Local 61 Records, 1943-1990 AIS.1989.05
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America Local 61, I.
  - USA Grinding, 1987-1988 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Shasta, National Labor Relations Board, 1986-1988 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1985-1987 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Shasta Negotiation Proposals, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Agreement between Shasta and IUMSWA, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Labor Reports, January-July 1972 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - National Coal Mine Construction Agreement, 1981 (Box 50, Item 1)
  - National Master Freight Agreement and Eastern Conference Area Iron & Steel Rider, 1973-1976 (Box 50, Item 2)
  - Program of Blue Cross and Blue Shield Benefits, 1985 (Box 50, Item 3)
  - Layoff Notices, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Safety, 1969-1971 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - National Letters, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Negotiations, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Terminations, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Labor Reports, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Stephen Cukovich (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Overtime and Gate Pass Forms, 1972-1974 (Box 52, Item 1)
  - Labor Department, August-December 1972 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Layoff Notices and Safety Committee Meetings, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Paid Invoices, January 1981-May 1984 (Box 53)
  - Marine Equipment Catalog, 1987-1988 (Box 54, Item 1)
  - Census of Population, Number of Inhabitants: Pennsylvania, 1980 (Box 54, Item 2)
  - Census of Population, General Population Characteristics: Pennsylvania, 1980 (Box 54, Item 3)
  - General Services Administration, Office of Information Resources Management: Federal Telephone Directory, Region 3, 1983 (Box 54, Item 4)
  - The US Trade Deficit, 1985 (Box 54, Item 5)
  - Forward: Journal of Socialist Thought, January 1987 (Box 54, Item 6)
  - Census of Population, General Social and Economic Characteristics: Pennsylvania, 1980 (Box 54, Item 7)
  - Right to Know: Compliance Materials for Nonmanufacturers, 1986 (Box 54, Item 8)
  - Korean Phoenix: A Nation from the Ashes by Michael Keon, 1977 (Box 54, Item 9)
  - Factors Contributing to Economic Growth in Pittsburgh and Allegheny County: A Survey of Companies in High Growth Manufacturing Industries, 1984 (Box 54, Item 10)
  - Inside the Circle: A Union Guide to QWL by Mike Parker, 1985 (Box 54, Item 11)
  - Workers' Democracy, 1986 (Box 54, Item 12)
  - Special Bipartisan Committee to Investigate Industrial Plant Closings, Final Report, 1984 (Box 54, Item 13)
  - All About OSHA (Box 54, Item 14)
  - OSHA Handbook for Small Businesses, 1979 (Box 54, Item 15)
  - Techniques of Harassment, 1979 (Box 54, Item 16)
  - International Economic Conversion Conference, June 22-24, 1984 (Box 54, Item 17)
  - Local 61 History, 1984-1986 (Box 54, Item 18)
  - Cast of Characters (Box 54, Item 19)
  - Eminent Domain Code (Box 54, Item 20)
  - Comparison of State Plant Closing Laws, 1984 (Box 54, Item 21)
  - David Roderick: Ice Ingot (Box 54, Item 22)
  - Plant Closings in Southwestern Pennsylvania: An Inventory and Survey by David Levdansky, 1984 (Box 54, Item 23)
  - Bureau of National Affairs: Collective Bargaining Negotiations and Contracts (Box 54, Item 24)
  - Bureau of National Affairs: Collective Bargaining Negotiations and Contracts (Box 55, Item 1)
  - Bureau of National Affairs: Union Labor Report (Box 55, Item 2-3)
  - The Developing Labor Law, 1971 (Box 55, Item 4-5)
  - Labor Law: Cases and Materials, 1986 (Box 56, Item 1)
  - Teamster Rebellion, 1981 (Box 56, Item 2)
  - Corporations in Crisis, 1963 (Box 56, Item 3)
  - Concessions and How to Beat Them, 1983 (Box 56, Item 4)
  - Nelson Directorate of Wall Street Research, 1984 (Box 56, Item 5)
  - Labor's Untold Story (Box 56, Item 6)
  - Global Reach, 1974 (Box 56, Item 7)
  - The Pastor as Prophet, 1985 (Box 56, Item 8)
  - Labor Research Review, 1983 (Box 56, Item 9)
  - What You Should Know about the Pension and Welfare Law, 1978 (Box 56, Item 10)
  - Walden and Civil Disobedience, 1966 (Box 56, Item 11)
  - Steel Workers Handbook on Arbitration, 1970 (Box 56, Item 12)
  - Union Labor Report, 1983 (Box 56, Item 13)
  - God's Agents for Change, 1983 (Box 56, Item 14)
  - Labor Crucible in the 1980's, 1986 (Box 56, Item 15)
  - Labor Tackles the Local Economy, 1986 (Box 56, Item 16)
  - Up Against the Gloom and Doom, 1984 (Box 56, Item 17)
  - Check Book (Box 56, Item 18)
  - Cancelled Checks (Box 56, Item 19)
  - Check Book (Box 57, Item 1)
  - Strip Tickets Big Bills (Box 57, Item 2)
  - Defense Fund Deposit Ticket (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Bulk Mail Receipts (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Bills, January 1970-June 1972 (Box 57, Folder 3-32)
  - Local 61 Financial Records, 1970s (Box 58)
  - Local 61 Payroll Sheets, 1952, 1954, 1960, 1962, 1964, 1968-1975 (Box 59)
  - Dravo Strike, 1985-1986 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Labor Board, 1983-1984 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Petitions, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - National Rand & File Against Concessions, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Survival Fund, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Denominational Ministry Strategy (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - IUMSWA Local 61 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Old Constitution (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Financial Request (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Amendments and Resolutions, 31st National Convention, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - IUMSWA Local 61 Legal Papers, 1970s (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - The Shipbuilder IUMSWA Newspaper, 1950s (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Transcript, Hearing at Glass Tower Hotel (Box 60, Item 1)
  - Dravo v. IUMSWA Local 61, 1984 (Box 60, Item 2)
  - Dwyer et al v. GAF Corporation (Box 60, Item 3)
  - Labor Notes, April 1988 (Box 60, Item 4)
  - IUMSWA Local 61 Forms (Box 60, Item 5-8)
  - Local 61 Assessment, 1985-1986 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Disbursement Vouchers, December 1970-May 1974 (Box 61, Item 1)
  - Cancelled Checks and Deposit Slips, 1972-1975 (Box 62)
  - Membership Cards, 1965-1974 (Box 63-64)
  - Membership Cards, 1971-1974 (Box 65, Item 1)
  - Becker v. Batson, Appealant's Brief, 1989 (Box 65, Item 2)
  - Becker v. Batson, Notice of Deposition, 1988 (Box 65, Item 3)
  - Becker v. Batson, Correspondence, 1984-1989 (Box 65, Item 4)
  - Becker v. Batson, Appearances, 1989 (Box 65, Item 5)
  - Becker v. Batson, Complaint, 1987 (Box 65, Item 6)
  - Becker v. Batson, Defendant's Answer to Plaintiff's Complaint, 1987 (Box 65, Item 7)
  - Becker v. Batson, Intervenor's Complaint, 1987 (Box 65, Item 8)
  - Becker v. Batson, Defendant's Response to Intervenor's Interrogatories (Box 65, Item 9)
  - Becker v. Batson, Opinion, 1983 (Box 65, Item 10)
  - Becker v. Batson, Reporter's Official Transcripts of Proceedings, 1988 (Box 65, Item 11-12)
  - Becker v. Batson, Appendicies II-IV (Box 65, Item 13-15)
  - Becker v. Batson, Appendix V (Box 66, Item 1)
  - Becker v. Batson, Judge's Opinion (Box 66, Item 2)
  - Neville's Ark Assistance Applications (Box 66, Item 3)
  - Pension Agreement between Metallurgical Exoproducts Corporation and IUMSWA Local 61, 1986 (Box 66, Item 4)
  - Ship Scope, Local 61 Newspaper, April 28, 1944 (Box 66, Item 5)
  - Shipbuilders Council of America, Statistical Summary, January 1986 (Box 66, Item 6)
  - Miscellaneous Papers (Box 66, Folder 1-4)
  - Negotiation, Meeting and Hearing Audio Cassettes, 1976-1987 (Box 66, Cassette 1-77)
  - Financial Ledgers, 1970-1984 (Oversize 1-2)
  - Protest Collage: IUMSWA Local 61, 1. (Map-case 3, Drawer 12)
  - Photograph of Downtown Pittsburgh, 2.
  - Photograph of Guanica 2 Barge, 3.
  - Photograph of Loaded Barge, 4.
  - Protest Against Dravo/Rally for Jesse Jackson, 1984; 5-7.
  - USWA Strike, Local 61 at Station Square, Pittsburgh, 8.
  - Local 61 Strike Against Dravo, 9-10.
  - Poster of Local 61 Wives Committee at the Democratic Convention, 1984; 11.
  - Local 61 Rally in Front of Union Headquarters, 12.
  - Photograph of Steel Mill, Neville Island, Pittsburgh, PA, 13.
  - Photograph from Local 61 Office: In Memoriam of Philip P. Murray, 14.
  - Photograph from Local 61 Office: In Memoriam of John J. Grogan, 15.
- Allegheny Conference on Human Development, II.
  This series contains information gathered by the Allegheny Conference on Human Development. Included are newspaper clippings, company annual reports, and correspondence concerning the research of the ACHD.
  - Samples (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Research to be Mailed (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Copies, "Listening: How to Do It and How to Get It Done to You" (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Related Pittsburgh Organizations (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - National Flag Foundation (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Papers (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Pamphlets (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Making Sense of Mr. Cyert (Box 67, Folder 8-9)
  - Washington and Jefferson College Mail-Ins (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - P-9 Hormel Strike (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Local 6 Harpoon (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Pittsburgh Pirates (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Research (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Tim, Research (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Strategy 21: Pittsburgh/Allegheny Economic Development Strategy to Begin the 21st Century, 1985 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Union Salaries (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Allegheny County Industrial Development Authority and the Allegheny Conference on Human Development (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Senator John Heinz (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Response to Crisis: Tri-State Conference on Steel (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - FCC Complaint: Finished Text (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Pittsburgh Conditions, Bibliography (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - South Africa/Divestment Movement (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Aliquippa (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Cyert Information (Box 67, Folder 25-27)
  - Pensions (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - Legislative Alerts (Box 67, Folder 29)
  - Bureau of National Affairs (Box 67, Folder 30)
  - Six Year Development Program, 1985-1990 (Box 67, Item 1)
  - McDermott International, Inc.: Annual Report for the Fiscal Year, 1986 (Box 67, Item 2)
  - McDermott International, Inc.: Report to Stockholders, 1986 (Box 67, Item 3)
  - Progressive Architecture, November 1972 (Box 67, Item 4)
  - Pittsburgh: Virtuoso Preservationists (Box 67, Item 5)
  - Here For You: Sewickley Valley Hospital, 1985 (Box 67, Item 6)
  - The Oliver Office Report: Pittsburgh, 1985 (Box 67, Item 7)
  - Blue Cross of Western Pennsylvania, Annual Report, 1983 (Box 67, Item 8)
  - The Grantsmanship Center News, May-June 1985 (Box 67, Item 9)
  - Pitt Magazine, March 1986 (Box 67, Item 10)
  - Canada Collects: Contemporary Sculpture from the Art Bank (Box 67, Item 11)
  - The Gothic Revived in Pittsburgh: A Medievalistic Excursion by James D. Van Trump, 1975 (Box 67, Item 12)
  - Pittsburgh Treasure Hunt by Patricia Wiley, 1981 (Box 67, Item 13)
  - Western Pennsylvania Development Credit Corporation, Annual Report, 1984 (Box 67, Item 14)
  - Allentown: A Survey of a Pittsburgh Community by the Residents and Business People (Box 67, Item 15)
  - United Way: New Directions (Box 67, Item 16)
  - Legend in Modern Gothic: The Union Trust Building, Pittsburgh by James D. Van Trump (Box 67, Item 17)
  - Girl Scouts of Southwestern Pennsylvania, Annual Report, 1984 (Box 67, Item 18)
  - Allegheny Trails Council, Boy Scouts of America, Annual Report, 1984 (Box 67, Item 19)
  - Skill-O-Rama: Allegheny Trails Council, Boy Scouts of America, May 17-19, 1985 (Box 67, Item 20)
  - The Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival, 1986 (Box 67, Item 21)
  - Prophetic Ministry and Church (Dis)Unity: The Sociological Paradox of Reconciliation by Theodore E. Long (Box 67, Item 22)
  - W&J: Washington and Jefferson College Magazine, 1985 (Box 67, Item 23)
  - The University of Pittsburgh Contact!, 1987 (Box 67, Item 24)
  - David Rosenberg and ACHD (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Research (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Japan (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Jones & Laughlin Pension (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Credits Authorized by Country, 1973-194 (Box 68, Folder 5-13)
  - Export-Import Bank (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Dravo Retirement Plan, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Forbes 500 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Tri-State Conference on Steel (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Korea (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Assessing the Blame for Economic Decline: The Denominational Ministry Strategy, The Mass Media and the Powers That Be by Michael Margolis and Robert E. Burtt, 1987 (Box 68, Item 1)
  - Introduction, Anthology of Greek Tragedy (Box 68, Item 2)
  - The Church and Labor Conflict in Post-Industrial Pittsburgh: New Alignments Around Old Dilemmas by Theodore E. Long, 1985 (Box 68, Item 3)
  - Export '85: RP~US Trade News, April 1985 (Box 68, Item 4)
  - Fortune, January 9, 1984, March 31, 1986 (Box 68, Item 5-6)
  - Directory of Companies Required to File Annual Reports with the Securities and Exchange Commission, 1984 (Box 68, Item 7)
  - Summary Plan Description of Retirement Plan 002 for Hourly Employees of Dravo Corporation Represented by IUMSWA Local 61 (Box 68, Item 8)
  - Export-Import Bank of the United States, Annual Report, 1979, 1981-1982, 1984 (Box 68, Item 9-12)
  - Report to the US Congress on Export Credit Competition and the Export-Import Bank of the United States, 1982-1984 (Box 68, Item 13-15)
  - World Economic Outlook, April 1985 (Box 68, Item 16)
  - United State Securities and Exchange Commission: Investment Company Act of 1940, 1982 (Box 68, Item 17)
  - United State Securities and Exchange Commission: Securities Act of 1933, 1975 (Box 68, Item 18)
  - Pittsburgh Business Times, 1985-1987 (Box 68, Item 19-21)
  - Dravo Pension (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Armco Pension (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - ACHD 501(c)(3) (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Power Chart (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Information for Brochures (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Agenda (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - ACHD Minutes (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Contribution Letter (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Hall Contract (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Allegheny Conference on Human Development (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - ACHD Bank Statements (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - ACHD Mailings, December 1986 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Bureau of Corporations (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - ACHD Phone (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - ACHD Members and Contacts (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - ACHD Letters Received (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - ACHD Research Packets (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - ACHD Business Manual Requests (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Allegheny Conference on Community Development (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Paper on Deindustrialization (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Homestead Industries, Coraopolis (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - ACHD, Letters Sent (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Thank You Letters to New Members (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Pittsburgh Press Articles (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Allegheny Conference on Community Development Chart (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - The Prophetic Ministry of the DMS Takes on Corporate Evil by Dale Hathaway, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 26)
  - Research (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - Denominational Ministry Strategy (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - Penn's Southwest Association (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - Regional Industrial Development Corporation (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Daley Report on Plant Closings (Box 69, Folder 31)
  - Mellon (Box 69, Folder 32)
  - Duquesne University Conference Copies (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Duquesne Light (Box 69, Folder 34)
  - Honeywell and Steel (Box 69, Folder 35)
  - Rosenberg Allegheny Conference on Community Development Committee Lists (Box 69, Folder 36)
  - Ahlbrandt, Jr., 1986 (Box 69, Folder 37)
  - Allegheny Conference on Community Development, Auerbach Thesis (Box 69, Folder 38)
  - From Community Protest by Frederick (Box 69, Folder 39)
  - Allegheny Conference on Community Development Money (Box 69, Folder 40)
  - Tax Documents (Box 69, Folder 41)
  - Allegheny Conference on Community Development Reports (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Strategy 21 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Allegheny Conference on Community Development Members, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania Foundation Directory (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Corporations Review, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 5-6)
  - The Carnegie (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Research (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Corporations Review, 1985-1988 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Allegheny County Air Quality Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Final Report, The Role of the Corporation in Community Economic Development as Viewed by 21 Corporate Executives by University Center for Social and Urban Research (Box 70, Item 1)
  - Pitt Magazine, April 1990 (Box 70, Item 2)
  - Oakland Library Consortium, Activity Report, 1988-1989 (Box 70, Item 3)
  - Technical Bulletin: Alternative Investing in Community Development (Box 70, Item 4)
  - Compact Disclosure (Box 70, Item 5)
  - Voice, October 1984 (Box 70, Item 6)
  - Bank Control of Large Corporations in the United States by David M. Kotz (Box 70, Item 7)
  - Pittsburgh Foundation, Annual Report, 1985, 1991 (Box 70, Item 8-9)
  - McDermott International (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Litman (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Denominational Ministry Strategy (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Requests for Annual Reports (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Applications for Aid, September 1986 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - University of Pittsburgh (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Research (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Returned Correspondence regarding 990 Forms (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Regional Industrial Development Corporation of Southwestern Pennsylvania (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Urban Redevelopment Authority Reports (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - The Presbyterian Valley Edited by William Wilson McKinney (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Amnesty International Newspaper Clippings (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Steel Valley Authority Newspaper Clippings (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Steel (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Papers (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Three Rivers Stadium (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Research (Box 71, Folder 19-20)
  - Corporations Review, 1985 (Box 71, Item 1)
  - The Pittsburgh Foundation... A Community Foundation (Box 71, Item 2)
  - The Pennsylvania Economy League (Box 71, Item 3)
  - Enterprise & Education Foundation: Private Enterprise Market System, Program Report, 1985 (Box 71, Item 4)
  - The Youth Project, Annual Report, 1985-1986 (Box 71, Item 5)
  - Penn's Southwest Association, Annual Report, 1984 (Box 71, Item 6)
  - Pittsburgh Council on Higher Education is... (Box 71, Item 7)
  - Public Parking Authority of Pittsburgh (Box 71, Item 8)
  - Toward Tomorrow: An Environmental Scan for the United Way of Allegheny County, 1985 (Box 71, Item 9)
  - Pitt Magazine, September 1986 (Box 71, Item 10)
  - W&J: Washington and Jefferson College Magazine, 1985-1986 (Box 71, Item 11)
  - Communique by Vectors/Pittsburgh, SEptember 1986 (Box 71, Item 12)
  - Richard King Mellon Foundation, Annual Report, 1985 (Box 71, Item 13)
  - Carnegie Mellon: The Professional Choice (Box 71, Item 14)
  - Private Enterprise Market System Teacher's Guide: Money, Inflation and Jobs (Box 71, Item 15)
  - Redevelopment Authority of Allegheny County (Box 71, Item 16)
  - Daisytown: Old Times in a Mining Community, 1981 (Box 71, Item 17)
  - Allegheny Conference Education Fund, Five Year Report (Box 71, Item 18)
  - Mellon Bank Corporation, Community Report, 1985 (Box 71, Item 19)
  - Mellon Bank Corporation: Prepared for the '90s, Annual Report, 1989 (Box 71, Item 20)
  - The Public Education Fund: The First Two Years, 1983-1985 (Box 71, Item 21)
  - Countdown to Renaissance II: The New Way Corporate America Builds by Robert McLean III, 1984 (Box 71, Item 22)
  - Prelude to the Future (Box 71, Item 23)
  - Foundations (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Directory of Pennsylvania Foundations (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Letters of Recommendation (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Form 990 Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Tax Forms (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Foundations, Source Book Profiles (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Duquesne University (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Cyclops Corporation, Annual Report, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Foundation Annual Reports (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Corporate Flight (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Law Firms (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Press Clippings (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Proposed Economic Development Program Budget (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Coalition for Christian Outreach (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Research (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - PNC Financial Corporation (Box 72, Folder 17-33)
  - Parkvale Savings Association (Box 72, Folder 34-36)
  - Uni-Marts, Inc. (Box 72, Folder 37-40)
  - Mestek, Inc. (Box 72, Folder 41-43)
  - Mellon Bank (Box 72, Folder 44-49)
  - Astrotech International Corporation (Box 72, Folder 50-53)
  - Blair Corporation (Box 72, Folder 54-56)
  - The Penn Traffic Company (Box 72, Folder 57-58)
  - Kennametal Inc. (Box 72, Folder 59-61)
  - Michael Baker Corporation, Form 10-Q, October 1, 1989 (Box 72, Item 1)
  - Michael Baker Corporation, Form 10-K, 1989 (Box 72, Item 2)
  - USX, Annual Report, 1988 (Box 72, Item 3)
  - Mellon Bank Corporation: Agenda for Reality, Annual Report, 1990 (Box 72, Item 4)
  - Notebook (Box 72, Item 5)
  - Labor Notes, April 1988 (Box 72, Item 6)
  - News Briefs: American Maritime Officers Service (Box 72, Item 7)
  - Pittsburgh Business Times, July 1987 (Box 72, Item 8)
  - ACTION Housing, Annual Report, 1985 (Box 72, Item 9)
  - Carnegie Mellon, Annual Report, 1985-1986 (Box 72, Item 10)
  - ACTION-Housing, Inc.: Twenty-five Years of Housing and Neighborhood Improvements, 1982 (Box 72, Item 11)
  - The Pittsburgh Convention Center (Box 72, Item 12)
  - Mellon Bank Corporation, Director Interlocks, 1985 (Box 72, Item 13)
  - Greater Pittsburgh Chamber of Commerce Report, 1985-1987 (Box 72, Item 14-15)
  - Penn's Southwest Association, Annual Report, 1987 (Box 72, Item 16)
  - The Public Education Fund: The First Two Years, 1983-1985 (Box 72, Item 17)
  - Dravo Corporation (Box 73, Folder 1-4)
  - Allegheny Ludlum Corporation (Box 73, Folder 5-7)
  - L.B. Foster Company (Box 73, Folder 8-9)
  - Tuscarora Plastics, Inc. (Box 73, Folder 10-16)
  - USX Corporation (Box 73, Folder 17-20)
  - Legent Corporation (Box 73, Folder 21-22)
  - Ampco Pittsburgh Corporation (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - First Federal of Western Pennsylvania (Box 73, Folder 24-25)
  - Action Industries, Inc. (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - Michael Baker Corporation (Box 73, Folder 27-29)
  - Autoclave Engineers, Inc. (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Astrotech International Corporation (Box 73, Folder 31)
  - Salem Corporation (Box 73, Folder 32)
  - Reed International (Box 73, Folder 33)
  - Mellon Bank Corporation (Box 73, Folder 34-35)
  - The Penn Traffic Company (Box 73, Folder 36)
  - Uni-Marts, Inc. (Box 73, Folder 37)
  - PNC Financial Corporation (Box 73, Folder 38-41)
  - Integra Financial Corporation (Box 73, Folder 42)
  - First Western Bancorp, Inc. (Box 73, Folder 43)
  - Equimark (Box 73, Folder 44)
  - DQE (Box 73, Folder 45)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation (Box 73, Folder 46)
  - Consolidated Natural Gas Company (Box 73, Folder 47)
  - Robertson-Ceco Corporation (Box 73, Folder 48)
  - Henley Shareholder Services (Box 73, Folder 49)
  - Timken Company (Box 73, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence with Companies (Box 73, Folder 51)
  - Mellon Bank Corporation, 2nd Quarter Report, 1990 (Box 73, Item 1-2)
  - First Federated of Western Pennsylvania, Annual Report, 1989 (Box 73, Item 3)
  - Michael Baker Corporation, 1989-1991 (Box 73, Item 4-7)
  - Westinghouse, Annual Report, 1988 (Box 73, Item 8)
  - Aristech, Annual Report, 1988 (Box 73, Item 9)
  - Rochester & Pittsburgh Coal Company, Annual Report, 1989 (Box 73, Item 10)
  - Pitt-Des Moines, Inc., Annual Report, 1989 (Box 73, Item 11)
  - Company and Organization Research and Reports (Box 74-77)
  - Miscellaneous Papers and Notes (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Flyers and Newsletters (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, David Rosenberg (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Articles (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 78, Folder 5)